本字幕由 ShinY 深影字幕组 原创翻译制作
深影字幕组论坛地址 http://shinybbs.com
翻译： fanfan Alice 带着猫咪私奔 许块块
校对： 许块块   后期： 唱唱反调
现在我们记起你了 我们需要你回来
We remember you now. And we need you back.
所以 亲爱的孙女
So please, my darling granddaughter,
请你告诉我们 你在哪
just tell us, where are you?
塔米辛 你在干什么?
Tamsin, what are you doing?
- 我们终有一天会死去 - 停车
- We all gotta die some day. - Stop the car.
塔米辛
Tamsin!
不
Noooo!
有人在那 快出来
Someone's in there. Come on out.
我不会伤害你的
I'm not gonna hurt you.
我还是不会伤害你... 很重的哦
I'm still not gonna hurt you... much.
放轻松 放轻松
Take it easy, take it easy.
嘿 我不会伤害你的
Hey, I'm not gonna hurt you.
当你不知你是谁时 生活会很艰辛
Life is hard when you don't know who you are.
当你知道真相后 生活会更艰难
It's harder when you don't know what you are.
我的爱伴随死神的降临
My love carries a death sentence.
我迷失了多年 在藏匿中找寻
I was lost for years, searching while hiding.
那个不为人知的属于我的世界
only to find that I belong to a world hidden from humans.
但我已厌倦躲藏
I won't hide anymore.
我要过自己想要的生活
I will live the life I choose.
第四季 第二集 睡美人学院
4x02 - Sleeping Beauty School
你有香槟 巧克力
You got champagne, chocolate.
又丝滑又实在的巧克力
both lube and actual chocolate.
而我从维多利亚的秘密超模那得了真传
And I got a lead on some Victoria Secret models.
亲爱的 我不是在说什么画册
And I'm not talking catalogue, hon.
我说的是走秀台
I'm talkin' runway.
天使级别质量
Angel quality.
肯吉 你在干什么?
Kenz, what are you doing?
看啊! 我准备了她最喜欢的东西
Ta da! I got her favourite stuff.
有丝袍 眼罩还有 玉米热狗
I got silk rope, blindfolds, corndogs.
我们还没有找到她
We haven't found her yet.
这不过是时间问题 你懂的
Well, just a matter of time. You know that.
塔夫特那里情况如何?
What about Taft's observatory?
没有结果 没有发现什么痕迹 它完全消散了
There's nothin', no scent. It's completely gone.
特里克还有黑尔呢?
Trick, Hale?
黑尔在摆弄她的塔罗牌和电话
Hale is monitoring her cards and phone,
特里克在地下安装了试探器
Trick's got feelers in the underground,
但是还是没有找到
but so far nothing.
她不可能直接消失不见是吧?
Well it's not like she just disappeared into nothing, right?
不管哪个怂人掳走了她 我肯定
I'm sure she's just super pumped from super-sucking
她现在超级抑郁痛苦
to death whatever ass-fart took her.
你有可能是对的
You're probably right.
当然
Course I am.
必须的
D 请告诉我有条线索了
D, please tell me we have a lead.
你怎么不下楼看看
Why don't you come downstairs.
我的老天 那简直是小版的我 那是谁?
Oh my god it's mini-me. Who is that?
我在那找到她
I found her at the site.
你觉得她看到了那场车祸?
You think she saw the crash?
我想她就置身于车祸中
I think she was in the crash.
- 你一定在骗我 - 瓦科基里有很多条命
- You've gotta be shitting me. - Valkyries have many lives.
我想她更像是克隆出来的
I just figured she'd be more like clone-y.
塔米辛是最后一个看到波的人
Tamsin was the last person to see Bo.
在卡车里 她说了一些关于波父亲的话
And in the truck, she said something about Bo's father.
波甚至不知道关于她父亲的一切
Bo doesn't even know anything about Bo's father.
不过有可能她知道
Well maybe she does.
所以我们得审问她
Then we got to go all interrogation on her.
看看她到底是谁
Find out who she is for real.
我们不想吓到她 她有可能会抓狂
We don't want to frighten her. She might lash out.
如果她是塔米辛 她会杀死你
And if she is Tamsin, she tried to kill you.
- 就像那样 - 是的
- There is that. - Yeah.
不过她有可能不是塔米辛
But she might not be Tamsin.
闪开 废柴 我要去玩了
Peace out, losers. I'ma go play.
待会见
Later.
- 那是塔米辛 - 塔米辛
- It's Tamsin. - Tamsin!
该死
Oh, dammit.
- 你没事吗? - 没事
- You okay? - Yeah.
- 你需要什么吗? - 谢了 我不用
- If you ever need anything. - Thanks. I don't.
所以她不可能给我们任何信息
So she can't give us any information.
科基里如果复生
When Valkyries are reborn,
他们的记忆恢复得慢而且散乱
their memories come back slow and scattered.
而且很显然她们的头发茂密而有光泽
And apparently their hair full and lustrous.
在这个时候 他们脆弱又有价值
At this age, they're vulnerable and valuable.
但是他们的记忆 会慢慢恢复的 对吗?
But her memories, they will come back eventually right?
瓦科基里和死人的灵魂打交道
Valkyries deal in the souls of the dead.
他们在人的一生里看到如此多屠杀
They see so much carnage in one lifetime
所以她们有时会抑制下一个肉身的记忆
that sometimes they repress those memories in the next.
靠
Shit.
- 注意说话 - 又来了
- Language. - Again.
是的 但是太慢了 她是最后一个看见波的人
But yes, c'est tres poopy, she was the last one who saw Bo.
这个地方是个死亡圈套
This place is a death trap.
让我把这句绣在枕头上
Remind me to embroider that on a pillow.
又来了
Again.
我看鸭池都比这安全
I've seen duck ponds with better security.
你怎么还活着
How are you still alive?
特里克 塔米辛是我们找到波的最后希望吗?
Trick, is Tamsin really our last chance of finding Bo?
还有其他的办法
There is one other way.
你的手臂怎么了?
What happened to your arm?
我们需要导航仪器
We need a certain directional device.
你落在英格拉姆的指南针
The compass you left behind at Engelram's.
哦 这个家伙?
Oh, this bad boy?
- 你个小偷 - 又来了
- You little thief. - Again.
你有没有看到我的浑天仪
Have either of you seen my Armillary Sphere?
好了 你们去忙活的时候
Okay. Well, while you guys are working on that,
我打算做点什么事
I'm gonna go do a couple things.
你哪都不能去
You are not going anywhere.
- 她不需要照顾 - 又来了
- This does not babysit. - Again.
你玩我吧
Could have fooled me.
这是糖衣炮弹吧 不可错过哦
It's about yay big, encrusted in rubies? Hard to miss.
我不过是用网游来教育孩子
Okay. I'm just really educating the child in the ways of internet hilarity
看一个动物熊跳江南Style
watching an animated bear dance to "Gangnum Style"
不过是生活的基本需求
is a basic life necessity. Well...
你还是可以继续教育她所谓的基本需求
Well you can continue educating her in the basic necessities
还有保证她安全 黑尔和我会去找波
and keep her safe. Hale and I will find Bo.
不要啊
Hells no.
- 注意用词 - 又来了
- Language. - Again.
- 戴森 - 肯吉 这没有商量的余地
- Dyson. - Kenzi. This is not a discussion.
- 你得放我走 - 肯吉 不许走
- You have to let me go! - Kenzi, you're not going.
- 又来了 又来了 又来了 - 安静
- Again, again, again, again! - Quiet!
- 你知道波在哪? - 我知道她不在哪
- Do you know where Bo is? - I know where she's not.
根据这个罗盘 她不在这个物质地球上了
Because according to this compass she's no longer on this physical plane.
又来了
Again.
有人吗?
Hello?
怎么周围天旋地转的
Oh, everything's spinning.
不是旋转 是在动
Not spinning, moving. Wha...
动?
Moving?
靠
Shit.
特里克 你要告诉我们到底发生了什么吗?
Trick, are you gonna tell me what really happened?
我可以闻到阿尔菲的血在你身上
I can smell Aife's blood on you.
她被我伤到了
She was wounded... at my hand.
当符咒破解的时候我们想起了波那是好事
When the spell was broken and we remembered Bo, there was joy.
但是对于阿尔菲
But for Aife,
她能想起来的就是失去了孩子
there was only the memory of losing her child,
现在她快要被逼疯了
and she was driven back to insanity.
很抱歉
I'm sorry.
波永远都不能知道
Bo must never find out.
很多东西她都不会知道
There's a lot of things Bo must never find out.
所以 追踪者希留斯退休了
So, trackers. Helios is retired.
摩的瓦正在监狱 只有艾比斯利
Moldavia's in prison. There's Ebisu,
不过他是个傻瓜
but he's an idiot.
不 那还有一个人
No. There's only one person who can
他可以横贯存在的相交平面
transverse the intersecting planes of existence.
恩底弥翁 他可是个传说
Endymion? He's legendary.
而且失踪了八百年
And, for the last 800 years, elusive.
只有一个人能告诉我们他在哪
There's only one Fae who might be able to tell us where he is.
莎琳娜
Selene.
他的前妻 开了一家美术馆
His ex. She owns a salon.
尤那达人
The Una Mens.
他们不是在阿什那里嘛
I thought they set up base in the Ash's compound.
他们在审问人
They're pulling in people for "interviews."
重建规则是一个庞大的活
Restoring order is a messy business.
折磨 死亡 狩猎 痛苦 之类的
Torture, death, man-hunts, pain. The usze.
这是痛苦的样子?
Is this what pain looks like?
不 这是在圣卢西亚做水疗
No, this is a spa weekend in St. Lucia.
拜托 不要
Please. No more.
告诉我们你对莫里根的尸体做了什么
Tell us what you have done with The Morrigan's body.
她躲在我书桌上的油画后
She was behind the portrait above my desk.
但是她跑掉了 那个讨厌的村姑在嘲笑我
But she escaped. That wicked wench is toying with me.
她没有死 她只是失踪了
She's not dead. She's missing.
她没有死 失踪而已
She is dead. She is missing.
你说的中间必有一个谎言 或者都是
One of those things is a lie. Or both.
那个小妓女还好好活着
That evil little tart is very irritatingly alive.
我用祖先的名义发誓
I swear on the graves of my family.
我们该把你送去见你祖宗
It was our mistake to not count you amongst those graves.
生命给予幻术师太大的力量
This life gives too much power to the last Mesmer.
而你不过白白浪费
You are but waste.
不要 不要
Please, please no!
不 别 不 等一下
No, please, please! No, no wait!
- 我会给你想要的 - 感兴趣
- I'll give you what you want. - Interested.
- 不是艾芙妮 - 不感兴趣
- Not Evony. - Not interested.
一些极其更有价值的
Something infinitely more valuable.
为什么我要给你的疯女人
Why would I give you a crazy bitch,
既然我可以给你她
when I could give you her.
接受 你被释放了
Accepted. You are released.
做一个小调整
With one minor adjustment.
欢迎来到莎琳娜家 男士们 我能帮你什么
Welcome to Selene's, gentlemen. What can I help you with?
涂指甲? 刮胸毛?
Mani-pedi? Chest wax?
- 擦亮你的徽章? - 我们在找人
- Polish your badges? - We're looking for someone.
我们都一样啊 亲爱的
Aren't we all, darling.
旧事重提 恩底弥翁
A blast from the past. Endymion.
艾迪 我的罗德・斯图尔特 好几年了
Eddy? Oh my Rod Stewart, it's been years.
你是知道他在哪 我们需要立刻找到他
Of you know where he is, we need to find him immediately.
先娱乐后工作
Pleasure before business.
有人告诉我你们这些不守规矩的
Something tells me those unruly curls
卷毛控制不住自己
aren't going to manage themselves.
我们通常不让顾客自己预约
We don't usually let customers make their own appointments.
事实上我是...
Actually I was just...
你是来找 艾迪 你想从他身上得到什么
You were looking for Eddy. What do you want with him?
这是警察的事
It's police business.
你知道莎琳娜准备把你们排成一排踹走
You know, Selene's gonna string you along for a kick,
但是她不会告诉你
but she's not gonna tell you shit.
所以你要做的就是去见爱思特德
So what you need to do is go and see Astrid.
你需要见她给她个信息
And you need to go and give her this message.
这是印度语
This is Hindi.
等等 我还不知道你的...名字
Wait, look, you know I didn't get your... name.
你找到了什么吗?
Did you get anything?
别担心 我有线索了
Yeah don't worry, I got a lead.
不错 我有满脑子信息
Good, all I got was a head massage.
- 戴森是你的男友吗 - 不是
- Is Dyson your boyfriend? - Nyet.
- 你有男友吗? - 没有 男人都蠢
- Do you have a boyfriend? - Negative. Men are stupid.
你曾经有男友吗
Did you ever have a boyfriend?
用这个身体? 见鬼
With this bod? Hel... heck yeah.
- 你为什么分手了? - 很复杂
- Why'd you break up? - It's complicated.
你还爱他吗?
Didn't you love him anymore?
我知道了 你认为爱就是最根本的
I know, right? You think that love's going to be the ultimate,
然后你认为要放弃所有的
then you realize that it means giving up more than you knew.
你做了个决定 它把你困在了恼人的盒子
You make a decision and it kicks you in the freakin' box
然后让你想这如果还值得去爱
and leaves you wondering if it's ever worth loving again!
无所谓了
Or whatever.
谁是黑尔? 可爱吗
Who's Hale? Is he cute?
他是一个朋友 一个警察 警察朋友
He's a friend. A cop. A cop friend.
避孕套是什么?
What's a condom?
好吧 不不 你得...
Okay, no, no, no, no, no. You gotta...
嘿
Hey!
尖锐的东西 不能碰
Hey hey hey, sharp objects! Not for you.
这是波的房间 只能她进
Look, this is Bo's room. Bo only.
我不想你动她的东西
I don't want you touching her stuff.
我甚至不想你看她的东西
I don't even want you looking at her stuff, okay?
你在干什么
What are you doing?
为什么你在晃 是因为瓦科基里的事吗
Why are you vibrating? Is it a Valkyrie thing?
我得去尿尿
I have to pee.
哦 我不需要跟你去 是吧
Oh, I don't need to, like, be there for that, do I?
- 不 - 好吧 去吧
- No! - Well okay, go on then!
谢谢
Thank you.
不不 你在干什么
No, no, no, no, no! What are you doing?! Oh!
我需要它变异种 这是我唯一的希望
I need that to be Fae.! It's my only hope!
塔米 对不起 别哭
Oh Tam-Tam honey. Honey, I'm sorry. Please don't cry.
别哭了 都是我的错
Please don't cry. It's all my fault.
愚蠢的肯吉 那面霜是我的伪装
Stupid Kenzi. It's just that the cream, it's my disguise.
是魔法 你想看吗
It's magic, it's magic. Do you want to see it?
好 看这
Okay, okay. Here.
好
Okay.
小女孩和瓦科基里
Little girls and Valkyries,
我现在展示的是肯吉娜拉的俄罗斯魔法
I present to you the Russian magic of Kenzlana.
再来一次
Again.
对不起 我做不成 没有面霜 没有闪光
Sorry kid, can't do it. No cream, no gleam.
但是我们能做饼干
But um, we can make cookies.
不 这我没法做
No. This I cannot do.
写这个的女人不想让你们找到他
The woman who wrote that doesn't want you to find him.
她希望你的记忆抹去
She wants your memories erased.
还有很多消息
Well there's a lot of that goin' around.
金发的很沮丧 另一个也是
The blonde one is frustrated. The other one too.
你去找一个猎人 需要勇气去捕猎
You seek a hunter. And you seek the courage to hunt.
我不知道你在说什么
I don't know what you're talking about.
我没有说话 我不能说话
I don't talk. I cannot talk.
阿斯顿米 很荣幸
An Astomi. It's a pleasure.
我也是 你们两个很符合
Mine too. For one who gets her sustenance
她的食物的口味 你们两个是可口的美味
from the scents around her, you two are a tasty treat.
为什么你不抹去你的记忆
Why didn't you erase our memories?
我已经香化面霜和洗发水
I've been perfuming creams and shampoos
在莎琳娜那里好几年了
at Selene's for years.
在那工作的女人是恶魔的化身
The women who work there are evil incarnate.
12年以后我的烫发还没有出来
12 years later, and my perm still hasn't grown out.
- 你会帮我们吗 - 这是我的荣幸
- Will you help us? - It would be my pleasure.
这是一支吻 只有一个时候可以用到
This is one kiss. Only one moment will be its match.
- 对不起 - 你会得到你想要的
- Excuse me? - You will get what you need.
至于你的失意 去找你爱的人
And for your frustrations. Go to the one you love.
我已经幻想过无数次这样的场景了
I've had several fantasies that started just like this.
你真不应该回来
You really shouldn't have come back.
你对我说谎
You lied to me.
我认为是你回答问题的时候了
I think it's time you answered some questions.
女孩们 吃饭时间到了
Girls, it's feeding time.
猜下谁会来吃晚餐
And guess who's coming to dinner?
喔
Whoa.
这就是你的幻想 所有女孩拿着棍子样的东西
So this fantasy of yours, all the girls carrying pokey things?
不 唯一棍子的东西 就是我的
Nope. There was only one pokey thing. And it was mine.
- 你叫什么 - 谁管呢 他就像美味零食
- What's your name? - Who cares. He's snackilicious.
他闻起来就是纸杯蛋糕...
He smells like cupcakes...
和新洗的衣裳
And fresh laundry...
那个强・汉姆
And Jon Hamm.
爱思特德对我们做了什么
What did Astrid do to us?
不是我们 是你
Not us. You.
我饿了
I'm hungry.
黑尔 我得走了...
Hale, I, I gotta...
你去找莎琳娜 艾迪 做你该做的
Yeah, go find Selene, find Eddy. Do what you gotta do.
我欠你一个人情
I owe you one.
对你欠我50个
Yeah, you owe me like 50.
所以你和波一起住 那意味着你们爱对方吗
So if you and Bo live together, does that mean you love each other?
当然 那是完全的永远的好朋友
Totally. But it's strictly BFF's.
- 想舔一下吗 - 什么是最好的朋友
- Here, wanna lick? - What's BFF?
就像两个人在一起会为对方做任何事
Well. It's when 2 people would do anything for each other
总会得到另一方的回报
and have always got each other's backs.
就像 如果有一个人有麻烦了
Like, if one's in trouble,
另一个会解决它们
the other gets them out.
如过有一方难过了 另一方会化上闪耀的眼妆
If one's sad, the other puts on sparkly eye make-up
带他们出去跳舞
and takes them out dancing.
如果一个不见了 另一人用最小的暗示
If one's missing, the other has even the tiniest inkling
就知道他们在哪
of where the they are.
但是波不见了 你不知道她在哪
But Bo's missing and you don't know where she is.
我知道 讨厌
I know. I suck.
喔!
塔米辛 我不是告诉你别动任何东西
Tamsin, I told you not to... touch anything!
妈的 这是波吗
Holy dildos! Is that Bo?
- 哦 好吧 - 着着火呢
- Ow, ow, ow. Okay. - It's burning, it's burning!
- 没用的废话 - 这变糟糕了 变糟糕了
- Oh crapity crap. - It's getting worse. It's getting worse!
好吧 详情报道 我知道了
Okay, Play-by-play, I get it.
M M X V 这意味这什么
M M X V. What does that mean?
我不知道 也许一些疯狂的预言字母
I dunno, probably some crazy Fae word.
D会知道的
D-Man will know.
你认为波被困在卡里了吗
Do you think Bo's stuck in the card?
精细
Subtle.
我在巴黎时候很久就没看见过了
I haven't seen one of these since my time in France.
如果记忆管用的话 也需要很多的手感
If memory serves, it takes a great deal of finesse
去解开1879年的约瑟夫・劳克
to unlock a 1879 Joseph Loch.
艾迪
Eddy.
Eddy!
艾迪你最好没死
Eddy! You better not be dead.
没有死 亲爱的 就是沉沉的睡着了
Not dead, darling. Just fast, fast asleep.
波
Bo?!
不是波
Not Bo.
笨手笨脚的人 你认为你来这干什么
Hey butterfingers, what do you think you're doing over here?
重新装修
Redecorating?
下一次在桌子上放花或者其他的
Well next time, put flowers on the table or something.
我不知道发生什么了 我就是...
I don't know what happened. I just ...
就是说你从来没有在你生命中
What happened is you've never waited a table
当过服务员... 不管你简历上这么说
a day in your life... Despite what your resume says.
我认为...我丢了我的胸牌
I think I... I think I lost my name tag.
没事 我们都在逃离一些事 安柏
It's okay. We're all running from something, "Amber."
我总是制造麻烦
I always make such a mess.
你就是那种笨手笨脚的人
You are kind of a huge klutz.
但是你很可爱 有趣
But you're also cute, and funny.
而且性感
And... sexy.
你认为我很有趣?
You think I'm funny?
我认为你需要喝一杯 今晚打烊后
I think you need a drink. Tonight, after closing.
我不能 对不起 我就是不能
I can't. I'm sorry, I just can't.
他真是漂亮
He's just so beautiful.
艾迪 醒醒 醒醒
Eddy, wake up man. Wake up.
只有我能做到 亲爱的
Only I can do that, sweetheart
但是我不会为你这么做
and I'm not about to do it for you.
- 你会叫醒他的 - 如果不呢?
- You will wake him. - Or...?
我会把你用牙撕成碎片
I'll tear you to pieces with my teeth.
保证会先打我屁屁?
Promise to spank me first?
如果必须的话
If that's what it takes.
两个字 偏不
Two words. Nuh-uh.
叫醒他
Wake him!
忘了艾迪吧 他出局了
Forget Eddy. He's out.
狼人来了
The wolf is in.
至少他将会的 只要一个吻就可以办到
Or at least he will be. And all it will take is just one kiss.
一个吻 我就是你的囚徒?
One kiss and I end up your prisoner?
只有在你睡着的时候
Only when you're asleep.
再多一个 我就任你处罚
Then one kiss more and I'm all yours to punish.
知道这些就够了
That's all I needed to hear.
现在吻他
Now kiss... him.
- 发生了什么事? - 艾迪?
- What's happening? - Eddy?
海洛特
Harlot.
艾迪 我需要你的帮助
Eddy, I need your help.
当然 但是先帮我绑住这个妓女
Of course. But first, help me bind this trollop.
然后我们可以谈谈我欠你多少 好心人
Then we can talk of the great debt I owe you, kind sir.
蜂蜜酒 我请客 或者土耳其浴
Perhaps mead, on me. Or a Turkish bath.
我需要你帮我找到我爱的女人
I need you to help me find the woman I love.
这么重要的人 她叫什么
And what is the name of this magnificent creature?
波
Bo.
你是对的 肯吉
You're right, Kenz,
开锁是每个女人的必备技能
lock-picking is skill every woman should know.
肯吉? 我知道这个名字 它是…
Kenz? I know that name. It's...
哦 不
Oh no.
嗨 外面有人吗
Hey! Is anybody out there?
- 终于 - 嘘 你会吵醒了他
- Oh! Finally. - Shhhh. You'll awaken Him.
他?
Him?
我不能说
I don't think I can say.
漂亮的眼睛 棕色和蓝色
Beautiful eyes. Both brown and blue.
你就是那一个
You are the one.
这是哪儿? 他是谁?
What is this place? Who is "He?"
你惹他生气了
You made him angry.
这都是你的错
This is all your fault!
她大概五英尺六英寸 棕色眼睛
She's about 5'6, brown eyes,
白人 长棕色头发
Caucasian. Long brown hair...
先生 这仅是波的描述
Sir, this is merely a description of Bo.
我需要你告诉我关于她的事情
I need you to tell me about Bo.
好 她是嫌犯吗?
Right, is she a suspect?
你的意思是我们要谈论
You mean like, "She dances like no one's watching"
"她跳起舞来旁若无人"?
are we talkin' about?
不 我需要知道你的心在哪里 和她的心
No, I need to know where your heart lies, and hers as well.
- 她的心是她自己的 - 不完全是你的?
- Her heart is her own. - Not entirely yours?
- 她有个女朋友 - 啊 背叛了你的婊子
- She has a girlfriend. - Ah, the betrayal of a strumpet.
再说一遍我把你的舌头割下来
Say that again and I will rip out your tongue.
真对不起
My apologies.
但是你有她出界的证明吗?
But do you have renderings of these transgressions?
- 看 - 你是从哪里得到这个的?
- Hey. - Where did you get this?
- 肯吉 - 又一个情人
- Kenzi. - Another lover!
- 她是… - 你们是彼此的恋人?
- She's... - You are Kenzi's and Kenzi is yours?
不 她是我的
No! She's mine!
我的朋友 只是朋友
Mine friend. My friend.
一个朋友
A friend.
如果波在那张卡上 她就有大麻烦了
If that is your Bo on that card, she's in a heap of trouble.
艾迪 你必须帮我
Eddy, you have to help me.
抱歉 我不答应
Apologies, but no.
你饿了吗? 我突然很想吃羊肉
Are you hungry? I've a sudden craving for mutton.
她有最美的心灵
She has the most beautiful heart
每一次她爱的人受伤她都会心碎
and it breaks every time someone she loves is hurting.
她很勇敢 固执 很有激情
She's brave, stubborn, she's passionate...
真诚
true.
她爱起来倾尽所有
She loves with all of her being.
没了她我什么也做不成
And I can't do any of this without her.
- 现在 还那么困难吗? - 不了
- Now, was that so difficult? - No.
你刚刚做的…
Yeah. What you just did, that's...
那么大声说出来 很困难
Sayin' it out loud like that, that's hard.
说出你的心最深切隐秘的欲望
Yes, to delve into the innermost sanctum of the heart's desires
常常被认为是一个人最艰难的旅程
is oft deemed one of life's most arduous journeys.
- 黑尔 你要告诉她 - 谁?
- Hale, you gotta tell her, man. - Who?
别逃避了
Don't do that.
肯吉 你要告诉她你的感觉
Kenzi, you gotta tell her how you feel.
- 好吧 那个… - 啊 原来她是你的
- Okay, that... - Ah, so Kenzi is yours.
那不容易 好吗? 只因为你确定
Hey, it's not that easy, all right? Just because you're sure...
波爱的是劳伦
Bo is in love with Lauren.
但是我仍然为她战斗因为我知道我的感觉
But I still fight for her because I know how I feel.
- 是的 你知道 我们要找到波- 不 不
- Yeah, you know, we need to find Bo, so... - No, no...
格鲁达要来了 你的家庭不同意
The Garuda is coming; Your family won't approve;
你太胖了 三年都过去了 黑尔
your pants are too tight. It has been 3 years, Hale.
你爱她 而她就在你眼前
You've been longing for her and she's right in front of you.
好的
Okay.
太好了 我说过 这值得在最难喝的
That was wonderful! I said, it calls for a
酒吧里来一杯庆祝
drink at your most unsavoury watering hole.
- 我们有事要做 - 好吧
- You and I have work to do. - Yes.
- 一份肝和洋葱 - 谢谢 亲爱的
- One liver and onions. - Thank you, darling.
别走太远 你很漂亮
Now don't go too far. I do like that view.
我觉得那个男人刚用他的眼神抽了我的屁股
I think that guy just slapped my butt with his eyes.
你是怎么忍受这样的顾客的
How do you put up with some of these customers?
员工不也忍过来了嘛?
Same as I put up with some of the staff.
对不起 如果之前我很不礼貌但是
I'm sorry if I was rude earlier but...
好的道歉不会包含 "如果" 和 "但是"
No good apology ever included the words "if" and "but."
嗯 我是个混蛋 好些没?
Uhm, I'm a jerk. Better?
我是个自我为中心的混蛋?
I'm an egocentric jerk?
别太为难自己 公主
Don't be too hard on yourself, Princess.
也别太为难他们
And don't be hard on them either.
特别是打屁股的事情 我也想做啊
Especially about the butt thing. I'd slap that.
你总比那个笨蛋强
Yeah well better you than bonehead ...
- 天哪 他噎住了 - 什么?
- Oh my god, he's choking. - What?
天哪
Oh my god.
帮我放倒他 帮我放倒他
Help me get him down, help me get him down.
天哪
Oh my god.
你是加纳多样异种 对吗?
You're a Ghanian Diversity Fae, right?
谢谢
Thank you. Phew!
你知道我们能用这个赚多少吗?
Do you know how much we can make for this?
我录下了整个关于外星人的过程
I've recorded the whole alien thing.
奥托和我是很好的联盟
Otto and I were great allies,
但赢了拉克菲尔德战斗的是我
but it was I who won the battle of Lechfield.
那很好 怎么
That's great. How...
我怎么做到的? 我转移了他们的注意力
How did I do it? Why, by diverting attention using a
就用了一个涉及到烟雾
clever technique involving smoke,
五维位移和一头吵闹的牛的
a total of five dimensional
很聪明的小技术
shifts and the loud braying of cattle.
嗯 所以关于空间位移
Okay, so these dimensional shifts,
我们要在他们之间移动 怎么才能做到呢?
we have to move between them right? How do we do that?
这很复杂
It's complicated.
我爱的女人在那里 并且还有危险 拜托了
The woman I love is out there, and she's in danger. Please.
如果我找不到你的波我还会有这些吗?
If I couldn't find your Bo, would I have these?
我们被跟踪了
We're being followed.
戴森 我们需要找到矛盾处
You see, Dyson, we need to find an inconsistency.
一个变换?
A shift?
一个在时间和物理上都断断续续的事物
A stutter of either the temporal or physical realms.
艾迪 我觉得我们两者都有
Eddy, I think we have both.
看 同一个男人同时出现在两个地方
Look, the same man appears in two places at once.
- 都超越时间 - 干得好
- Both move out of time. - Good work.
学生变成了老师 当然我在开玩笑
And the student becomes the teacher. I jest of course.
当然 那我们怎么办?
Of course. So now what do we do?
我们去打个招呼
We go say hello.
肯吉 你是个男人 我是个女人
Kenzi, you're a man, I'm a woman.
肯吉 你是个女人
Kenzi, you're a woman,
我是个男人 所以这说得通
I'm a man, so it only makes sense.
喔 这真蠢
Wow, that is stupid.
嘘
Shhhh.
我用了五首艾薇儿的歌
It took like five Avril Lavigne songs to get Baby Tam-Tam
才让塔米睡着 你打扰到她
a ticket to play-time land. You wake her Sk8er Boi,
你就负责去处理她
you are dealing with her.
你知道整整五首艾薇儿的歌词?
You know the words to five Avril Lavigne songs?
黑尔…你真好
Hale... That is so sweet.
这些能够给波的房间多加点装饰
These are gonna add that little boom-boom-pow Bo's room needs.
- 怎么了? - 我要告诉你一些事
- So wassup, Siren? - I need to tell you something.
你们找到艾迪了吗 他是一个跟踪能手?
Did you guys find Eddy? Is he a total tracking genius?
- 算是吧 但是… - 但是什么? 你们
- Kind of. But... - But what? Do you guys
找到关于波的踪迹没有?
have a lead on Bo or not?
你能不能消停一会儿?
Can you just stand still for a second?
你的表情怎么这么扭曲? 波出事了?
Why are you so twitchy? Is it Bo?
她变成金色头发了? 啊 我怎么在开玩笑?
Is she blonde? Ugh, why am I joking?
发生了什么? 黑尔 告诉我
What is happening? Hale, talk to me.
我喜欢你
I like you.
每次我一走进房间 就只能看见你
Every time I walk into a room, you are all I can look at.
你有一个人类所少有的风范和力量
You have so much style and strength no human should have.
我希望能参与你的生活
I want to be a part of that.
我也希望成为你的一部分
I want to be a part of you too.
- 啊 好诡异 - 好的诡异?
- Ugh, this is weird. - Good weird?
这没关系吧 对吗?
This is all right, right? Right.
- 等等 - 少说话 多做事
- Wait, wait. - Less talking, more everything else.
哦天哪 我喜欢你穿紫色
Oh god, I love you in purple.
等等 是因为香水吧
Wait, it's the perfume.
它闻起来像一段好时光
Oh it smells like a good time to me.
它是个咒语
It's a spell.
塔米辛
Tamsin.
天啊 波莎 德杰尼勒斯
Holy Portia DeGeneres,
夏奇拉 戴维李罗斯
Shakira, David Lee Roth.
我醒来就这样了
I woke up and this happened!
要命啊 我最多醒来长丘疹
Shit, all I've ever woken up with is a zit.
- 我丑爆了 - 你还好啦
- I'm hideous! - Yeah, you're really not.
这是什么突发状况?
Is this some kind of spurt?
你以为我是谁? 瓦科基里的斯波克医生?
Who do I look like? Dr. Spock's Guide to Growing Valkyries?
我哪知道 她要是这进度
Well, I don't know! If she keeps this up,
周二就能赶上贝蒂・怀特了
she's gonna be Betty White by Tuesday.
没事的 亲爱的 一切都会好的
Here honey, it's okay. It's gonna be okay.
- 好吧 - 黑尔 跟她说一切都会好
- Okay.  - Hale, tell her everything's gonna be okay!
- 一切都会好的 因为... - 嗯嗯
- Everything's gonna be okay 'cause ... - U-huh...
- 天啊 头发 - 我们身体本来就会成长
- Oh my god, the hair! - ... as we grow our bodies change.
世事无常 大概正常嘛
Stuff happens. Mostly normal.
这还正常? 这也太大了吧
This is normal? But these things are so big.
看起来傻不? 我还能跳绳吗?
Are they stupid? Can I still jump rope?
- 不 - 好了 你还是先走吧
- No... - Oh yeah, maybe you should just go.
黑尔 跟我跳起来
Hale, jump with me!
不不不
No no no.
坏瓦科基里 我是说 坏黑尔
Bad Valkyrie. I mean, bad Hale.
黑尔要走了 但肯吉 我们可没谈完
Hale has to go now. But Kenzi, we are not done talking.
我感觉超级诡异
I feel super bizzaro.
很抱歉通知你 孩子 这可从不会消失
Well I'm sorry to tell you, kid, but it's never goin' away.
这是成长的必经之路
It's just part of growin' up.
"热狗" 我从没吃过这么恶心又
"Smog dog." I've never had anything so equal parts
- 美味的东西 - 艾迪 这是什么?
- disgusting and delicious. - Eddy, what is this?
看起来像自动贩卖机啊
Well it looks like some sort of condiment dispenser?
什么
What?
艾迪 这是异种 我看不懂这方言 不过
Eddy, this is Fae. I can't read the dialect but...
你在莎琳娜睡了多久啊
How long were you asleep at Selene's?
几年吧 也许几百年
A few years. Perhaps a few hundred.
可我从不会错的
But I'm at right as gold.
你个傻子 你不会追踪
You're obsolete, man. You can't track.
你连这玩意是啥都不知道
You don't even know what this thing is.
我当然知道 就是几排按钮嘛
Of course I do. It is a simple sequence of buttons.
如果你打开另一个维度大门 没有票的话
If you open the gate to another dimension without a ticket
我们都完蛋了
and we all go kaboom.
噢 不!
Oh no!
- 你还好吗? - 喔...
- Are you okay? - Ow...
啊 你弄疼我了
Ohh... Oh, you hurt me.
我很抱歉 艾迪 你还好吗?
I'm sorry. Eddy, are you okay?
你为何跟踪我们 为何费尽心思
Why are you following us? Why are you so hellbent
阻止我和艾迪一起工作?
on stopping me from working with Eddy?
他不是艾迪
He is not Eddy.
我是艾迪
I'm Eddy.
这女人叫西里欧 她可是个贼
This woman's name is Clio and she is a thief of identities!
我能怎么办 你中了莎琳娜的魔咒
What was I supposed to do while you were under Selene's spell,
并困在她的腿间要求服务
and between her legs? Requests for your services were coming in.
所以你吸取了他
So you took his gigs.
我最后记得把你塞进了裙子里
The last one that I recall put you in a hell of a dress.
他在急着造人...
All he was doing was making babies.
等等 难道艾迪是你...
Wait, is Eddy your...?
不不 他的卵都是自作聪明的元素
No. No, his spawn are giggling dim-witted Elementals.
- 可你就是元素 - 等着瞧
- But you're an Elemental. - With a twist.
这些元素只能控制四种元素之一
Those Elementals only have command one of the four elements.
我能控制所有
I commune with all of them.
这让我与众不同 比你强百倍
Which makes me very special and so much better than you.
骗子!
Lies!
看到了吗? 从土中得知 那个人在此处
See? For example, from the Earth, that a man was killed
被杀了六十五年之久
exactly in that spot 65 years ago.
可从水中得知 当时湿度是百分之三十二左右
And I can tell from the water, that the humidity is exactly 32 or 33%.
恩底弥翁啊 有火车正驶来
And Endymion, I know that a train is coming.
你真是惹错人了
You have made a grave error in crossing me.
我四步就登上珠峰了
I mounted Everest in four strides,
也曾登顶二十处子
and mounted the twenty virgins that live atop.
有歌儿赞颂我
There have been songs celebrating me.
是啊 在一二九五年
Yeah, in 1295.
哥们 你现在碌碌无名了
Dude, you're all washed up.
# 飞过大海 越过草坪 #
O'er the sea and across the glen,
# 迎来了月神恩底弥翁 #
comes the great and noble Endymion.
# 死亡和黑暗他公然违抗 #
Death and darkness he doth defy,
# 想要杀他 他是不死之身 #
Try to kill him, and he will not die.
好吧 下趟车八点十五到
Okay. So the next train comes at quarter after eight.
我们需要张票 你有吗?
So we're gonna need a ticket. Do you have one?
也许有哦
You know, I might.
是火车票? 什么是Mmxv?
It's a train ticket? So what's MMXV?
那些不知如何发音的东西
Whatever unpronounceable thing that is.
那是罗马数字 二零一五
They're Roman numerals, 2015.
我猜时间是晚上八点十五
I'm guessing a time: 8:15 PM.
要是快点我们还赶得及
If we hurry, we can make it.
没人能碰卡片却不被烧到
No one can touch the card without being burned.
我能
I can.
- 她是元素 - 火烧不到我
- She's an Elemental. - Fire can't touch me.
我们可以谈谈我的价钱
We should talk about my price.
要什么给什么
You'll get whatever you're owed.
能等下吗? 谢谢你
Can we... can we have a second? Thank you.
好吧 首先 这什么元素的妹子有点神经质
Okay, A: Chickie-poo Elemental seems a little ele-mental.
其次 她要把卡片拿走耍我们怎么办
B: She could take the card and bone us big.
最后她的皮肤完美无瑕 我太恨她了
And C: Her skin is suspiciously flawless and I hate her so much.
肯吉 你必须得呆在这
kenez, you have to stay here.
戴森 求你了
Dyson, please.
塔米辛也许会记得什么事 好吗?
Tamsin might remember something. All right?
再说了 黑尔还要找你聊聊
And besides, Hale wants to talk to you about something.
他来的时候 耐心听听好吗?
And when he does, please try and listen to him, okay?
- 好吧 - 时间不等人哦
- Right. - Time's-a-ticking.
拜
Bye.
开弓没有回头箭
Once we do this, there is no going back.
我也没办法承诺 我能保护你
And I can't promise you that I'm gonna be able to protect you.
你是谁? 你为什么想要救我?
Who are you? Why did you try to save me at Engelram's?
嘿 我看到一小伙在派对上有麻烦
Hey! I saw a guy at a party in trouble
还能顺便赚钱 何乐不为?
and the chance to make a buck. Okay?
我不相信
I don't buy that.
你是警察 还有你的侦探朋友 她叫...
You're a cop, okay, and your sleuth friend, what's her...
- 肯吉 - 肯吉 我看你潜力不错
- Kenzi. - Kenzi. I saw you as potential competition,
在我的地盘探头探脑 我决定来看看你
who was busting in on my territory and I decided to check you out.
结果是我多虑了
And it turns out that I have absolutely nothing to worry about.
- 我能开始了吗? - 时间不等人
- So can I please do this? - Time's-a-ticking.
好的
Okay.
天啊 竟然有用啊
Oh man, that worked!
- 你怀疑过? - 没有 呃 也许有吧
- You're surprised? - No. I mean, maybe.
因为 这种多维度东西太难预测了
Because, ya know, this multidimensional stuff is quite unpredictable.
戴森
Dyson.
你的伤口怎么样了? 缝针愈合了吗?
So how's your incision? Did the stitches heal?
- 劳伦 - 戴森 我想回家
- Lauren. - Dyson, I want to come home.
他们还在找你 很不安全
They're still looking for you. It's not safe.
其他人呢? 波呢?
What about the others? What about Bo?
戴森 我很害怕
Dyson, I'm scared.
劳伦 我不知道你是最棒还是最糟的对手
Lauren, I don't know if you're the best rival or worst, but I know
但我知道 你聪明伶俐 足智多谋
this, you are smart and you are resourceful.
不管要做什么 你快做吧
So whatever needs to get done, you do it.
因为目前来看 你孑然一身
Because right now you're on your own.
谢谢 戴森 请照顾好她
Thanks. And Dyson, take care of her, please.
我会付他们付你的三倍价钱
I'll give you triple what they're paying ya.
亲爱的 我当然付得起
Of course I can afford it, darling.
全族灭绝的好处就是
The positive of having your entire race obliterated
继承了一大笔遗产啊
is that you inherit one big bloody bank account.
可是有句话要说清楚
But we must be clear about one thing.
波必须完完整整的活着
Bo must be alive and in one piece.
说定了?
Now do we have a deal?
当然
Absolutely.
你个小妖精 让我都激凸了
Well, erect my nipples, you are a naughty little minx.
再跟我讲一次 慢慢地
Tell me again... slowly.
- 我们说定了 - 什么说定了?
- Uh, we have a deal. - What deal?
我不能说 是客户的私人保密信息
I cannot reveal that. That's privileged client information.
可是...
But...
你有我的血誓
you have my blood oath
我会找到你的淫妖
that I will find your Succubus.
该死 好戏上演了 那是死亡列车
Shit's about to get interesting. That's a Death Train.
想都别想
Uh, uh, uh. Don't even think about it.
稍安勿躁 今晚路途遥远
Hold onto your knickers. Tonight's gonna be a wild ride.
是的 没了 再没有了 跟魔力永别
Yes, gone. No more. Sayonara magic tinkle powers.
你今晚能见我吗?
Can you meet me tonight?
我能付起 好的到时见
Duh, I can pay. Yeah I'll see you there.
- 感觉好些了? - 我压跟没感觉
- Feel better? - I barely feel anything.
我要尿尿啦
I'm gonna go pee.
密码 该死
Password. Shit.
也许就是"该死"呢
Maybe it's "shit."
托德 我小时候狗的名字
Toad. It was my dog's name when I was a kid.
T-o-a-d 很讽刺吧?
T-O-A-D. It's ironical, huh?
我刚看你天气预报呢
I was just looking for your weather app.
八六二三 你看吧
8623. You can go ahead.
看起来是晴天 你没信我 对吧?
Look it's sunny, with a side... You're not buying this, are you?
这是那个外星视频
This is about that alien video.
你知道多少人付钱要这玩意吗?
Do you know how much people will pay for shit like this?
这不是外星人 这视频不存在
Look, it wasn't an alien, but this video cannot exist.
有些坏人在追我
There are some very bad people after me,
他们要是看到这个 会找到我
and if they see this, they'll come for me.
我真想多告诉你些 可是...
I wish I could tell you more, but it's just...
真很复杂
It's complicated.
要是你在我手机上删东西 我就有这福利
If this is what I get for letting you delete things on my phone
那我该让你知道 我有超过三十张
I should let you know, I have over 30 Instagrams
在加油站拍得三明治照片
of gas station sandwiches on here.
- 我是劳伦 - 很高兴见到你 劳伦
- I'm Lauren. - It's nice to meet you, Lauren.
谢谢你
Thank you.
够了 够能量离开了
Just enough. Just enough to get out.
该走了
It's time to go.